<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>New South Wales on Paperesque theme example</title>
    <link>http://example.com/tags/new-south-wales/</link>
    <description>Recent content in New South Wales on Paperesque theme example</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2011-2020 Fabian Tamp</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.com/tags/new-south-wales/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wood Swallow</title>
      <link>http://example.com/posts/wood-swallow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/posts/wood-swallow/</guid>
      <description>The Wood Swallow &amp;ndash; Project Gutenberg
  This Wood Swallow has been long known to ornithologists1, but unfortunately under so many generic and specific appellations, that it may be cited as an instance of the manner in which our science has been burthened with useless names, thereby producing an inextricable confusion2, and which in this instance, by a reference to Latham’s accurate description, and the slightest care on the part of other writers, might have been avoided.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pied Crow Shrike</title>
      <link>http://example.com/posts/magpie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/posts/magpie/</guid>
      <description>Editor&#39;s note: This page is marked as a draft, which is why everything is orange and stripey.
  The Pied Crow-Shrike &amp;ndash; Project Gutenberg
  This species was originally described and figured in White’s ‘Voyage to New South Wales’: it is consequently the oldest and most familiarly known member of the group to which it belongs. It is very generally distributed over the colony of New South Wales, inhabiting alike the brushes near the coast, those of the mountain ranges, and also the forests of Eucalypti which clothe the plains and more open country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leach&#39;s Kingfisher</title>
      <link>http://example.com/posts/leaches-kingfisher/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/posts/leaches-kingfisher/</guid>
      <description>Specimens of this fine Kingsfisher are contained in the British Museum, the Linnean Society, and my own collections, all of which were procured on the north-east coast of Australia, where it evidently replaces the Dacelo gigantea of New South Wales and South Australia.
 Leach&#39;s Kingfisher &amp;ndash; Project Gutenberg
  The specimen in the Linnean Society’s museum was presented by Dr. Brown1, who procured it in Keppel Bay on the east coast; and it was subsequently seen at Shoalwater Bay2 and Broad Sound on the same coast; my own specimens were obtained at Cape York, the north-eastern extremity of Australia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great Brown Kingfisher</title>
      <link>http://example.com/posts/kookaburra/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/posts/kookaburra/</guid>
      <description>The Great Brown Kingfisher &amp;ndash; Project Gutenberg
  The Dacelo gigantea is a bird with which every resident and traveller in New South Wales is more or less familiar, for independently of its large size, which in itself would tend to attract attention, its voice is so extraordinary as to be unlike that of any other living creature. In its disposition it is by no means shy, and when any new objects are presented to its notice, such as a party traversing the bush or pitching their tent in the vicinity of its retreat, it becomes very prying and inquisitive, often perching on the dead branch of some neighbouring tree, and watching with the greatest curiosity the kindling of the fire and the preparation of the meal; its presence, however, owing to the quietude with which it passes through the forest, and the almost noiseless manner in which it settles, is seldom detected until it emits its extraordinary gurgling, laughing note, which generally calls forth some exclamation according with the temper of the hearer, such as “There is our old friend the Laughing Jackass,” or an epithet of a less friendly character: not unfrequently does its life pay the penalty of its temerity; for if, as is often the case, the traveller’s larder be ill-provided and his appetite keen, but a few minutes elapse before it is roasting over the fire it was lately surveying with so much curiosity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>